Hey everyone, a year or so ago, I had more or less given up on my travel coaching business.
After trying to do everything on my own, I just went quiet.
My website was still, I stopped posting on social media, and frankly I really didn't
know what to do.
But once I started working with Rogue Coach Teams, everything changed.
Not only did they help me market my business, they revived it.
They revamped my website, helped me revive my social media posting, walked with me to
get to clarify my niche, and considering how new coaching is in travel, they helped
with messaging, enabled my business to grow as it continued to refine its identity.
What I've appreciated most is how responsive, professional, and genuinely invested they've
been.
They've helped me get back on track, experiment with different ways of interacting with
my audience, and even helped me deliver webinars in a way that I was able to reach more people
and to have meaningful conversations about my travel coaching.
The growth hasn't been overnight, and that's okay.
What I appreciate is what it's given me, which is what I really needed.
Momentum, clarity, visibility, and the encouragement to keep showing up.
In many ways, they came at a point when I really needed the support because I had already
kind of surrendered to the idea that this business was not going to work.
I'm genuinely grateful for that.
And I can wholeheartedly and genuinely recommend the Rogue Coach Teams to anyone who's looking
for a team to help bring back their coaching, business back to life, and to give it a chance
to grow.